<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>bald &#8211; wylieisdbald</title>
	<atom:link href="http://localhost/tag/bald/feed/?simply_static_page=255" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 23:48:37 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>The Lucky Charm of Wylie ISD: Me!</title>
		<link>/the-lucky-charm-of-wylie-isd-me/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[local]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 23:40:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[#wyliebald]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bald]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[baldness]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=21</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Greetings, citizens of Wylie, As your illustrious Superintendent, I find myself in a reflective mood today, which I assure you is not solely due to the brilliant shine off my pristine, bald pate. No, dear readers, I am moved to reflect on the towering bastion of success that is Wylie Independent School District, and more [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Greetings, citizens of Wylie,</p>



<p>As your illustrious Superintendent, I find myself in a reflective mood today, which I assure you is not solely due to the brilliant shine off my pristine, bald pate. No, dear readers, I am moved to reflect on the towering bastion of success that is Wylie Independent School District, and more precisely, how your lives have been forever blessed by my leadership.</p>



<p>I&#8217;ve been told humility is a virtue. Indeed, if I possessed such a quality, I&#8217;d be quite humble about the magnanimity of my influence. But alas, your dear Superintendent David Vinson was not made for modesty. You see, like the bright chrome dome I proudly polish each morning, my achievements gleam in the bright light of day, visible for all to admire.</p>



<p></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
